{
    "id": "b9599eb51fe74973b0cfd5060d801f13",
    "title": "Would vs. Used to Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "325b6a11735f4c72bbba116f126fd642",
            "title": "Would vs. Used To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We ................................. go swimming every weekend.",
                    "description": "Both would and used to can be used to talk about past habits. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "used to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There ............................... be a coffee shop in that corner.",
                    "description": "Used to can refer to past states. Would cannot be used with this meaning. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "used to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ............................... spend hours talking to herself.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "used to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I was a kid, I ................................. swim a lot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "would",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There was no chance that my letter .................................... arrive in time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "would",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "On that train, he first met the woman he ..................................... one day marry.",
                    "description": "Would is the past tense form of will.",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "used to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you ........................................ get angry so easily.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would not",
                        "used not to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She asked if I ................................ like some advice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "would",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ................................. smoke.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "used to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ............................... like football, but now I don't.",
                    "description": "Used to can show past habits.",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "used to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ................................. hate him, didn't you?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "would",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I always .................................. be afraid of spiders.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "used to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}